<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rehearsal Assistant</string>
    <string name="about">Welcome to Rehearsal Assistant - beta 0.5.0</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="switch_to_simple">Switch to Simple Mode</string>
    <string name="switch_to_session">Switch to Session Mode</string>

    <string name="new_session_title">Enter a title for the session and click one of the \'Create\' buttons.</string>

	<string name="start_session">Click to Start Session</string>
	<string name="record">Click to Record</string>
	<string name="stop_recording">Click to Stop Recording</string>
	
	<string name="recording_instructions">Click the button to start the session. Click again to start/stop each recording. Use the MENU to stop the session.</string>
	<string name="recording_instructions_started">Click the button to start/stop each recording. Use the MENU to stop the session.</string>
	<string name="session_instructions">Session mode allows you to record multiple voice/audio annotations during an event. Such a documented event is called a session. Click \'Document New Session\' to create a new session and record annotations.  You may also click on an existing session to review its annotations, or long-press for more options.</string>
	<string name="simple_instructions">In simple mode, you can start/stop recording any time, and access the recordings from the list. Click on a recording to listen. Long-press to edit the recording\'s label. Use the MENU to e-mail all of the recordings.</string>

	<string name="playback_instructions">Click on an annotation below to listen. Long-press to edit the annotation\'s label. Use the MENU to e-mail the session.</string>
	<string name="annotation_label_text">Enter a new label for the annotation</string>
	<string name="no_annotations">No annotations were recorded for this session.</string>

<string name="license">Welcome to Rehearsal Assistant!\n\nBy
using this application, you agree to the following license:\n\nAndroid
Rehearsal Assistant\nCopyright (C) 2009 urbanSTEW\n\nThis
program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
(at your option) any later version.\n\nThis
program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.\n\nSee
http://www.gnu.org/licenses/ for a full text of the license.\n\nSee
http://urbanstew.org/rehearsalassistant/ for links to source code
and documentation.\n\n</string>

<string name="beta_warning">This software is in BETA status, which means
you are likely to encounter problems during use.\n\nIf you experience
problems, please e-mail a detailed description of the problem to comments@urbanstew.org
to help us resolve it.\n\nThank you!\n\n</string>
</resources>
